Ajay ko
kar do hua
hai
[music] hua hai ke ribbon kaise rahe hain
Welcome to this episode of Sandy's Chart of the Week
where all the old followers
know that I am continuously giving this for the 4th week,
Muslim time money has been made, only last
time it happened that Airtel's trend was
not triggered, that is, the tweet did
not get activated, so first of all I would
like to tell you that Airtel's
levels of last week are still valid, that is, the
level of Aar Paar which we have shared with you,
whenever this chart of Hui's money printing machine comes, it will
work with the same bangon power, you should note it down, so
this was the first, second title is
catch the train, print money, the biggest
mistake you people make is
catching the reed, I always try to
catch the trend, in catching the trend
I will say two-three things which I have tagged
because many times I get a message, sir,
do this in intraday or in swimming,
I say opportunity and in the fourth, do it in the first
swing, it means carry, so
first of all you should judge whether you have
enough money that you  Can you be patient
or not, if you don't have money then whatever you get
in intraday is your dream,
and if you have money and
want to carry trade in mutual then always keep one thing in
mind, if you want to buy something at 510 and
it is closing at 520 then always
write it down that its stoploss should be 515, that is,
₹15 will definitely come into the house,
if there is profit then there are bigger fools than us where
people have profit in their house but
later
we lose them in two ways, so these are some
things which you should keep in mind, that is,
first you judge your capacity whether
you are going to enter or the lion,
secondly if you are in profit then never do trailing,
hello and thirdly, I don't
know about others' trail, in which I share my view
with you, in the level that we give,
you will not lose without formation,
and to see the formation,
we have this permanent
stockist work size with you in the description of every video, you can watch
Supertrend sub's video from
that  You
can do COD after taking confirmation with hundred percent guarantee,
but if you are doing it straight without tax permission, then
that is completely your call, that is completely
your address, that is completely your judgment,
where you cut the race and I do
not like to track by running at all,
I believe that one should not trend until something is confirmed,
so I hope that
you must have understood the things, now let's start,
today is the 3rd trailer and that day before the train,
a great video is showing on your screen,
watch it, next week it will be
easier to earn money, it will be easier to apply for IPO, so
that you
can take the right decision and the right things and next also
that Bank Nifty sting, its video is
already life, so before starting the first trend,
I Mukul Agarwal
like your YouTube channel, whoever
must subscribe to the channel and
hit the bell icon, along with Twitter and
Telgram, if you join, you will keep getting
all the breaking news and date news of the stock market
before the first one, so
now today is the first raid,
this is a big vision of ICICI Lombard  This is a trail of
good thinking, a game with a little bit of a big
brain, and it says
that as the stock market is continuously
falling, its support point there, for
example, if you look at it, its low is 1520,
then f-18, 2837 and 3174, its channel life
support, listen carefully, channel wide support,
now what is our first duty, we should
not rush from anywhere, listen very carefully, make
money, the market has been in the past as well, as
you can see, continuously root canal, just one
day I
wrote this as an alarm clock, but the overall market has
fallen, so it means that the market is continuously
falling, we should never be in a hurry, now
if the market gives confirmation of buying anywhere at that point, then only
think about buying, otherwise when these levels break below,
like 1388 and 1374, only then will
we set the salary, but this is
such a level in whose area it has come,
it can give you a better opportunity, it
can give you a better chance, so I will track it and  I will
also go, you know, from Monday to
Friday I come live with you, in which I
take any of your stocks and give you the shares of my stocks,
so whenever I take some
such big stocks in which there is not a big current,
I
keep it continuous, like Bharti Airtel,
I have elastic until if it does not come
every day, every night, as I was saying that the level has
not come, but when it comes, we will do it, when it comes,
you should get a proper follow-up from this,
so we will keep that proper follow-up
in ICICI Lombard and along with it, like if you put
me on Twitter,
I will put it on Twitter or
you can follow it on Telegram, note down the level in paper,
this is the cafe level, if you
work in cash, do it, if you do
this, then do it in the war based on gas,
but never just that there is
support and if you run, then it will be a call for the whole, it will
arrest you, but
I feel this is a big setup, so I
shared it with you, so
next is GAIL India, the
support in GAIL India is 13250 and  The
resistance is 139 or how can I play the game now? The
market opens on Monday
at 13250. If you get confirmation, do it.
If it was 13252 and below it,
share the confirmation milk. Now
some uneducated people may say that he is saying both kinds of
things. So my brother, you can book any book,
any technical one. By the way,
take it there. A simple thing is that if this
is support and it breaks, it will turn.
You cannot get stuck by marrying it. So,
all this should be done. Unless you read books and get
education and do not remove it, you will never be
able to earn money. And our heartfelt
effort is to give you some positive,
some learning. If money is available, we are
trying to give you something from our heart and soul. So,
support 13250 turtle and
resistance more than 130 is alive or not. If I
ran on Sidhu, then we will talk
and if 13250 is broken, we will sell. Very
Christ, very Appear Again Gas.  The level of the
second and third deposit camp in which if it
again breaks positive 1325 then it will be buy, if it
remains 120 then it will be sell but let me remind you again these are
gas levels,
never initiate any link with wine without confirmation
otherwise you can keep it, you
can get stuck and for confirmation I would
like to show you one more thing, your big things will become
easy when you go to the playlist,
here in the playlist you will
see everything, it is called penny stocks, this WPS,
you will see everything if you
follow it correctly, then we and along with us the children who are
joining the class from the date are being
given to you on the screen in
which there is advanced geotechnical, similarly the
stock collection of the semester advance which has been taught to you inside bar, in
this way you
can easily earn money by clicking on any one, so keep earning money, keep
telling people thank you so much